Guide to the Stanford University Website Collection
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Schools, 2010-2011; Series 2
  - Earth Sciences, 2011-2013
    - Soil and Environmental Biogeochemistry, 2011-2012; soils20120907; 1044.5 megabyte(s) (2,777 files in 150 directories)
      - 2011 Oct 3, solis201110; 1167 megabyte(s) (3113 files in 162 directories)
      - 2012 Sep 7, soils20120907; 1044.5 megabyte(s) (2777 files in 150 directories)
    - Smart Fields Consortium, 2011
      - 2011 Sep 20, smartf201109; 215 megabyte(s) (220 files in 6 directories)
      - 2012 Sep 6, smartfields20120906; 216 megabyte(s) (190 files in 6 directories)
    - Solid-State NMR and Silicate Materials Group, 2011
      - 2011 Oct 24, geonmr201110; 2.87 megabyte(s) (136 files in 11 dirctories)
      - 2012 Oct 24, geo-nmr20121024; 2.69 megabyte(s) (101 files in 10 directories)
    - Vitousek BioGeoChemistry Lab, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Sep 20, vitou201109; 76.1 megabyte(s)
      - 2012 Sep 6, vitousek20120906; 61.2 megabyte(s) (433 files in 25 directories)
  - Education, Graduate School of, 2010-2012
    - School of Education, 2010-2013
      - 2010 Dec 13, education2011-005; 131 megabyte(s) (3027 files in 1134 directories)
      - 2012 Feb 10, education20120210; 230 megabyte(s) (7608 files in 122 directories)
      - 2013 Feb 8, ed20130208; 767 megabyte(s) (2607 files in 161 directories)
    - AAA Lab, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 4, aaalab201110; 107 megabyte(s) (346 files in 63 directories)
      - 2012 Sep 28, aaalab20120918; 59.8 megabyte(s) (337 files in 63 directories)
    - Center for Research on the Context of Teaching, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 4, crct201110; 272 megabyte(s) (186 files in 59 directories)
      - 2012 Sep 18, suse-crc20120918; 63.1 megabyte(s) (146 files in 55 Folders)
    - Center on Adolescence, 2011-2013
      - 2011 Jul 1, adol201107; 36.9 megabyte(s) (227 files in 36 directories)
      - 2012 April 12, adolescent20120412; 51.3 megabyte(s) (218 files in 36 directories)
      - 2013 Apr 8, coa20130408; 45.4 megabyte(s) (659 files in 64 directories)
    - Center to Support Excellence in Teaching, 2011-2013
      - 2011 Sep 6, cset201109; 237 megabyte(s) (197 files in 23 directories)
      - 2012 Jun 1, cset20120601; 157 megabyte(s) (233 files in 32 directories)
      - 2013 May 9, scet20130509; 194 megabyte(s) (760 files in 137 directories)
    - International Comparative Education
      - 2012 Feb 15, suse-ice20120215; 16.5 megabyte(s) (279 files in 57 directories)
    - Leadership Degree Programs, 2012
      - 2012 Feb 14, suse-ldp20120214; 3266.56 megabyte(s) (257 files in 76 directories)
    - Learning, Design, and Technology Program, 2012
      - 2012 Feb 14, suse-ldt20120214; 34.4 megabyte(s) (970 files in 111 directories)
    - Principal Fellows Program, 2011-2012
      - 2011 Oct 4, spfp201110; 0.57 megabyte(s) (53 files in 18 directories)
      - 2012 Sep 19, principal20120919; 0.61 megabyte(s) (54 files in 18 directories)
    - Stanford Teacher Education Program, 2012
      - 2012 Feb 14, suse-step20120214; 116 megabyte(s) (586 files in 76 directories)
    - Teachers for a New Era, 2012
      - 2012 Nov 7, tne20121107; 12.8 megabyte(s) (63 files in 19 directories)
  - Engineering, 2010-2012
    - School of Engineering, 2010-2013
      - 2010 Dec 8, 487 megabyte(s) (7214 files in 366 directories)
      - 2012 Jan 23, engineering20120123; 1658.88 megabyte(s) (18,429 files in 539 directories)
      - 2013 Jan 14, engineering20130114; 181 megabyte(s) (1733 files in 178 directories)
    - Aeronautics and Astronautics, Department of, 2011-2013; aa_2011-137
      - 2011 May 19, 404 megabyte(s) (526 files in 69 directories)
      - 2012 Mar 9, aa20120309; 406 megabyte(s) (586 files in 60 directories)
      - 2013 Mar 7, aa20130307; 294 megabyte(s) (656 files in 62 directories)
      - Structures and Composite Laboratory, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 24, structure201110; 203 megabyte(s) (549 files in 146 directories)
        - 2012 Oct 22, structure20121022; 92.8 megabyte(s) (296 files in 34 directories)
      - Unsteady Flow Physics and Aeroacoustics Laboratory, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 24, flow201110; 69.8 megabyte(s) (84 files in 14 directories)
        - 2012 Oct 22, flowgallery20121022; 75.1 megabyte(s) (80 files in 13 directories)
    - Bioengineering, Department of (Schools of Medicine and Engineering), 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 19, bio_2011-138; 107 megabyte(s) (595 files in 49 directories)
      - 2012 Mar 8, bioeng20120308; 164 megabyte(s) (639 files in 54 directories)
      - 2013 Mar 7, bioengineering20130307; 167 megabyte(s) (515 files in 35 directories)
    - Biomechanical Research Group, 2011
      - 2011 Oct 5, biomech201110; 3.55 megabyte(s) (221 files in 74 directories)
    - Center for Image Systems Engineering, 2012
      - 2012 Oct 16, scien20121016; 4434 megabyte(s) (16,010 files in 1141 directories)
    - Center for Integrated Systems, 2011-2013
      - 2011 Aug 2, cis201108; 473 megabyte(s) (1291 files in 158 directories)
      - 2012 May 7, cis20120507; 481 megabyte(s) (1292 files in 162 directories)
      - 2013 May 1, cis20130501; 634 megabyte(s) (1338 files in 167 directories)
    - Chemical Engineering, Department of, 2011-2012
      - 2011 May 19, cheme_2011-139; 20.6 megabyte(s) (418 files in 748 directories)
      - 2012 April 2, cheme20120402; 20.5 megabyte(s) (341 files in 57 directories)
      - 2013 Apr 1, cheme20130401; 38.3 megabyte(s) (324 files in 72 directories)
    - Civil and Environmental Engineering, Department of, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 19, cee_2011-141; 158 megabyte(s) (1061 files in 185 directories)
      - 2012 Apr 2, cee20120402; 208 megabyte(s) (1014 files in 174 directories)
      - 2013 Apr 1, cee20130401; 155 megabyte(s) (991 files in 196 directories)
      - Environmental Fluid Mechanics Lab, 2011-2013
        - 2011 Jul 22, emfl201107; 15.5 megabyte(s) (61 files in 7 directories)
        - 2012 May 1, efml20120501; 15.5 megabyte(s) (59 files in 7 directories)
        - 2013 May 1, efml20130501; 16.5 megabyte(s) (59 files in 7 directories)
      - John A. Blume Earthquake Engineering Center, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Jul 20, blume201107; 2713.6 megabyte(s) (3842 files in 104 directories)
        - 2012 Apr 20, blume20120420; 3993.6 megabyte(s) (883 files in 158 directories)
      - National Performance of Dams Project, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 13, npdp201110; 475 megabyte(s) (857 files in 41 directories)
        - 2012 Oct 4, npdp20121004; 7.76 megabyte(s)
    - Computer Science, Department of, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 19-21, cs_2011-140; 5990.4 megabyte(s) (10,467 files in 748 directories)
      - 2012 Apr 2, cs20120402; 5396.5 megabyte(s) (7175 files in 670 directories)
      - 2013 Apr 1, cs20130401; 4720 megabyte(s) (5959 files in 756 directories)
      - Security Laboratory, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 17, seclab201110; 108 megabyte(s) (353 files in 94 directories)
        - 2012 Oct 8, seclab20121008; 103 megabyte(s) (348 files in 94 directories)
        - Applied Crypto Group, 2011-2012
          - 2011 Oct 18-19, crypto201110; 6082.6 megabyte(s) (12,255 files in 1064 directories)
          - 2012 Oct 8, crypto20121008; 4884 megabyte(s) (12,190 files in 1,131 folders)
      - Human Computer Interaction Group, 2012
        - 2012 Jul 26, hci20120726; 4300.8 megabyte(s) (6510 files in 678 directories)
      - Visualization Group, 2012
        - 2012 Nov, vis20121112; 548 megabyte(s) (542 files in 84 directories)
    - Computer Systems Laboratory, 2011-2012
      The Computer Systems Laboratory is a joint lab of the Departments of Electrical Engineering and Computer Science located on the Stanford University Campus in the Gates Computer Science Building.
      Established in 1968, CSL is internationally recognized for its leadership in developing new ideas and trends in the design, organization, and use of computers. Research in CSL is both experimental and theoretical, traversing many domains: operating systems, computer networking, special architectures, compilers, programming languages, information management, graphics, security, reliability and fault tolerance, system specification and verification, user interfaces, integrated circuit design and special computer architectures.
      Teaching is formalized in the classroom, but constantly challenged and enriched through the hands-on work of the various CSL project groups and the wider influence of Silicon Valley technology. Of special interest is the Stanford Electrical Engineer Computer Systems Colloquium which is open to the public. The Colloquium is an ongoing guest lecture series touching on many elements of computer systems, the technologies they employ, and the systems they enable. Speakers are drawn form academia, commercial research labs, and industry.
      Students working in CSL are admitted to either the Electrical Engineering or the Computer Science department. Usually students with primary interest in VLSI, CAD, and computer architecture come from the EE department, while students with interest in compilers, operating systems, and programming environments come from the CS department. Because of the interdisciplinary nature of the lab, there are no rigid student classifications; undergraduates, Masters students and Ph.D. candidates from either department can work with any faculty member or any research project for which they qualify. It is just this interdisciplinary composition of the research teams that has proven the CSL to be a good environment for nurturing interesting and profitable ideas.
      Areas of Research: Core System Software Graphics Human Computer Interaction Information Management Security and Cryptography Systems Networking Ubiquitous Computing VLSI Architecture
      - 2011 Oct 6-7, csl201110; 3348.48 megabyte(s) (3683 files in 74 directories)
      - 2012 Sep 21, csl20120921; 2775 megabyte(s) (3626 files in 79 directories)
      - Center for Reliable Computing
        - 2012 May 22, CRC_2012-044; 12.7 megabyte(s) (218 files in 12 directories)
    - Electrical Engineering, Department of, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 20, ee_2011-142; 1515.52 megabyte(s) (4483 files in 1121 directories)
      - 2012 Apr 4, ee20120404; 1372.2 megabyte(s) (16,774 files in 1361 directories)
      - 2013 Apr 1, ee20130401; 1771 megabyte(s) (20,716 files in 2,005 directories)
      - Information Systems Laboratory, 2011
        - 2011 Jul 29, isl201107; 1413.12 megabyte(s) (808 files in 57 directories)
      - Magnetic Resonance Systems Research Lab, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 12, mrsl201110; 183 megabyte(s) (292 files in 76 directories)
        - 2012 Oct 3, mrsrl20121003; 164 megabyte(s) (356 files in 85 directories)
      - Space, Telecommunications, and Radioscience Laboratory, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 20-21, star201110; 3368.96 megabyte(s) (2480 files in 153 directories)
        - 2012 Oct 15, star20121015; 3359 megabyte(s) (2549 files in 157 directories)
    - Institute for Computational and Mathematical Engineering, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 23, icme2011-147; 367 megabyte(s) (678 files in 188 directories)
      - 2012 Apr 5, icme20120405; 550 megabyte(s) (713 files in 202 directories)
      - 2013 Apr 3, icme20130403; 486 megabyte(s) (647 files in 221 directories)
    - Living Matter Lab, 2012
      - 2012 Nov 27, biomechanics20121127; 612 megabyte(s) (1855 files in 318 directories)
    - Management Science and Engineering, Department of, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 23, mse_2011-143; 12.7 megabyte(s) (222 files in 42 directories)
      - 2012 Apr 5, mse20120405; 12.4 megabyte(s) (236 files in 49 directories)
      - 2013 Apr 3, mangsci20130403; 15 megabyte(s) (209 files in 40 directories)
      - Center for Work, Technology, and Organization, 2011-2013
        - 2011 Sep 9, cwto201109; 203 megabyte(s) (172 files in 16 directories)
        - 2012 Jun 7, wto20120607; 42 megabyte(s) (154 files in 16 directories)
        - 2013 May 20, wto20130520; 42.2 megabyte(s) (156 files in 16 directories)
      - Engineering Risk Research Group, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 10, errg201110; 5.85 megabyte(s) (83 files in 7 directories)
        - 2012 Sep 24, errg20120924; 5.81 megabyte(s) (84 files in 7 directories)
      - Systems Optimization Laboratory, 2011-2013
        - 2011 Sep 7, sol201109; 420 megabyte(s) (528 files in 51 directories)
        - 2012 May 31, sol20120531; 225 megabyte(s) (554 files in 53 directories)
        - 2013 May 8, sol20130508; 229 megabyte(s) (574 files in 56 directories)
    - Materials Science and Engineering, Department of, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 23, mat_2011-144; 8.19 megabyte(s) (254 files in 41 directories)
      - 2012 Apr 5, mat20120405; 8.63 megabyte(s) (212 files in 39 directories)
      - Brongersma Laboratory, 2012
        - 2012 Jul 24, brongersma20120724; 117 megabyte(s) (3440 files in 24 directories)
      - 2013 Apr 3, mse20130403; 7.1 megabyte(s) (199 files in 35 directories)
    - Mechanical Engineering, Department of, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 23, me_2011-145; 603 megabyte(s) (1609 files in 131 directories)
      - 2012 Apr 5, me20120405; 592 megabyte(s) (1718 files in 161 directories)
      - 2013 Apr 3, me20130403; 1935 megabyte(s) (1619 files in 175 directories)
      - Biomotion Laboratory, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 4, biomotion201110; 30.6 megabyte(s) (190 files in 18 directories)
        - 2012 Sep 19, biomotion20120919; 10.9 megabyte(s) (187 files in 24 directories)
      - Product Realization Lab, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 14, prl201110; 215 megabyte(s) (5597 files in 614 directories)
        - 2012 Oct 5, prl20121005; 123 megabyte(s) (352 files in 79 directories)
      - Thermal and Fluid Sciences Affiliates Program, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 24, tfsa201110; 25.7 megabyte(s) (76 files in 25 directories)
        - 2012 Oct 22, tfsa20121022; 3.26 megabyte(s) (73 files in 61 directories)
      - Thermosciences Group, 2011-2012
        - 2011 Oct 11, thermo201110; 1249.3 megabyte(s) (172 files in 18 directories)
        - 2012 Oct 2, thermosciences20121002; 855 megabyte(s) (124 files in 15 directories)
    - Stanford Artificial Intelligence Laboratory, 2011 Apr 8; 2.75 gigabyte(s) (6,005 files in 391 directories)
      Captured 2011 Apr 8
      The Stanford AI Lab (SAIL) is the intellectual home for researchers in the Stanford Computer Science Department whose primary research focus is Artificial Intelligence.
      Members of the Stanford AI Lab have contributed to fields as diverse as bio-informatics, cognition, computational geometry, computer vision, decision theory, distributed systems, game theory, image processing, information retrieval, knowledge systems, logic, machine learning, multi-agent systems, natural language, neural networks, planning, probabilistic inference, sensor networks, and robotics.
      - Stanford Artificial Intelligence Laboratory Dump And Restore Technique Archive
        Captured 2011 Apr 11.
        This website is an index of over one million SAIL file names and DART attributes.
        Although the SAIL computer celebrated 25 years of operation, 6 June 1966 through 7 June 1991, the DART tapes record only an 18 year span of 6,494 days. The first DART tape was written on Saturday 5 November 1972, and the last tape on Friday 17 August 1990. New files were created on 6,460 of those days.
      - Knowledge Systems, 2011 Jun 24
        KSL conducts research in the areas of knowledge representation and automated reasoning in the Artificial Intelligence Laboratory of the Department of Computer Science at Stanford University. Current work focuses on enabling technology for the Semantic Web, hybrid reasoning, explaining answers from heterogeneous applications, deductive question-answering, representing and reasoning with multiple contexts, knowledge aggregation, ontology engineering, and knowledge-based technology for intelligence analysts and other knowledge workers.
        - 2011 Jun 24, ksl_2011-164; 153 megabyte(s) (4368 files in 498 directories)
      - 2011 Apr 8-11, sail_2011-165; 2805.76 megabyte(s) (6005 files in 391 directories)
      - 2012 April 16, ai20120416; 5703.7 megabyte(s) (5759 files in 409 directories)
    - Stanford Engineering Everywhere, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 23, see_2011-146; 373 megabyte(s) (1436 files in 61 directories)
      - 2012 Apr 5, see20120406; 2119.7 megabyte(s) (1370 files in 55 directories)
      - 2013 Apr 3, see20130403; 2119 megabyte(s) (1332 files in 55 directories)
    - US/Asia Technology Management Center, 2011-2013
      - 2011 Sep 8, asia201109; 1802.4 megabyte(s) (3054 files in 256 directories)
      - 2012 Jun 6, asia20120606; 1874 megabyte(s) (2,750 files in 261 directories)
      - 2013 May 10, asia20130510; 1894 megabyte(s) (2831 files in 276 directories)
  - Humanities and Sciences, 2010-2012
    - School of Humanities and Sciences, 2010-2012
      - 2010 Dec 8, 86.8 megabyte(s) (774 files in 78 directories)
      - 2012 Jan 23, humsci20120123; 251 megabyte(s) (9,542 files in 253 directories)
    - African and African American Studies, Program in, 2012-2013
      - 2012 Mar 28, aaas20120328; 11.5 megabyte(s) (91 files in 24 directories)
      - 2013 Mar 4, aaas20130304; 112 megabyte(s) (93 files in 27 directories)
    - American Studies, Program in, 2011-2013; amstu_2011-108
      - 2011 May 11, amstu_2011-108; 93.9 megabyte(s) (195 files in 43 directories)
      - 2012 Mar 13, amstudies20120313; 73.8 megabyte(s) (163 files in 35 directories)
      - 2013 Mar 4, american20130304; 39.2 megabyte(s) (153 files in 43 directories)
    - Anthropology, Department of, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 9, anth_2011-102; 247 megabyte(s) (717 files in 32 directories)
      - 2012 Mar 5, anthro20120305; 203 megabyte(s) (784 files in 34 directories)
      - 2013 Mar 1, anthropology20130301; 315 megabyte(s) (1013 files in 44 directories)
    - Applied Physics, Department of, 2012-2013
      - 2012 Feb 8, appphysics20120208; 378 megabyte(s) (939 files in 761 directories)
      - 2013 Feb 2, appphysics20130212; 47.4 megabyte(s) (912 files in 787 directories)
    - Archaeology, Program in, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 11, arch_2011-109; 19.5 megabyte(s) (292 files in 45 directories)
      - 2012 Mar 13, archaeology20120313; 82.5 megabyte(s) (337 files in 61 directories)
      - 2013 Mar 4, archaeology20130304; 182 megabyte(s) (571 files in 69 directories)
    - Art and Art History, Department of, 2011-2012
      - 2011 May 4, art_2011-086; 98.6 megabyte(s) (4197 files in 1451 directories)
      - 2012 Feb 8, art20120208; 48.1 megabyte(s) (1697 files in 1196 directories)
    - Biology, Department of, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 5-7, bio_2011-097; 517 megabyte(s) (828 files in 47 directories)
      - 2012 Feb 7, biology20120207; 90.2 megabyte(s) (535 files in 24 directories)
      - 2013 Feb 19, biology20130219; 35.5 megabyte(s) (703 files in 24 directories)
      - Block Lab, 2012
        - 2012 Jul 24, block20120724; 124 megabyte(s) (372 files in 12 directories)
      - Luo Lab, 2011-2013
        - 2011 Aug 4, luo201108; 496 megabyte(s) (172 files in 11 directories)
        - 2012 May 8, luo20120508; 467 megabyte(s) (178 files in 12 directories)
        - 2013 May 3, luolab20130503; 256 megabyte(s) (185 files in 12 directories)
      - Walbot Lab, 2012
        - 2012 Nov 9, walbot20121109; 17.9 megabyte(s) (25 files in 6 directories)
    - Ethics in Society, Bowen H. McCoy Family Center for, 2011-2013; ethics_2011-123; 304 megabyte(s) (2665 files in 1073 directories)
      - 2011 May 17, 307.0 (2948 files in 1073 directories)
      - 2012 March 12, ethics20120312; 150 megabyte(s) (4252 files in 1119 directories)
      - 2013 Mar 6, ethicsinsoc20130306; 163 megabyte(s) (4748 files in 1247 directories)
    - Chemistry, Department of, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 5, chem_2011-098; 311 megabyte(s) (860 files in 199 directories)
      - 2012 Feb 6, chemistry20120206; 214 megabyte(s) (1787 files in 42 directories)
      - 2013 Feb 19, chemistry20130219; 93.8 megabyte(s) (3184 files in 36 directories)
      - Center for Molecular Analysis and Design, 2012
        - 2012 March 12, cmad20120312; 6.49 megabyte(s) (63 files in 16 directories)
      - Moerner Lab, 2012
        - 2012 Jul 31, moerner20120731; 125 megabyte(s) (275 files in 13 directories)
      - Wender Lab, 2012
        - 2012 Nov 9, pawender20121109; 107 megabyte(s) (1664 files in 89 directories)
    - Classics, Department of, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 4, classics_2011-087; 96.7 megabyte(s) (988 files in 93 directories)
      - 2012 Feb 8, classics20120208; 129 megabyte(s) (857 files in 80 directories)
      - 2013 Feb 11, classics20130211; 114 megabyte(s) (1125 files in 115 directories)
    - Creative Writing, Program in, 2012-2013
      - 2012 Apr 9, creative20120409; 599 megabyte(s) (756 files in 220 directories)
      - 2013 Apr 4, creative20130404; 506 megabyte(s) (1065 files in 339 directories)
    - Communication, Department of, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 9, comm_2011-103; 692 megabyte(s) (458 files in 242 directories)
      - 2012 Mar 5, comm20120305; 637 megabyte(s) (434 files in 195 directories)
      - 2013 Mar 1, comm20130301; 452 megabyte(s) (518 files in 219 directories)
      - Center for Deliberative Democracy, 2011
        - 2011 Jul 20, cdd201107; 172 megabyte(s) (536 files in 139 directories)
        - 2012 April 19, cdd20120419; 811 megabyte(s) (697 files in 177 directories)
      - Communication Between Humans and Interactive Media Lab, 2012
        - 2012 Jul 24, chime20120724; 4.09 megabyte(s) (45 files in 38 directories)
      - Institute for Communication Research, Political Communication Lab, 2011
        - 2011 Aug 15, pcl201108; 1300.48 megabyte(s) (1927 files in 132 directories)
        - Political Communication Lab, 2011-2013
          - 2011 Aug 15, pcl201108; 1300.48 megabyte(s) (1927 files in 132 directories)
          - 2012 May 21, pcl20120521; 640 megabyte(s) (2195 files in 130 directories)
          - 2013 May 6, pcl20130506; 541 megabyte(s) (2379 files in 131 directories)
    - Comparative Studies in Race and Ethnicity, Program in, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 11, csre_2011-111; 103 megabyte(s) (125 files in 7 directories)
      - 2012 Mar 13, crse20120313; 116 megabyte(s) (218 files in 10 directories)
      - 2013 Mar 4, crse20130304; 63.4 megabyte(s) (220 files in 10 directories)
      - Native American Studies, 2012
        - 2012 Jul 31, nas20120731; 3.28 megabyte(s) (58 files in 4 directories)
      - Comparative Studies in Race and Ethnicity (Undergraduate Major/Minor)
        - 2012 Aug 14, comparative20120814; 2.35 megabyte(s) (100 files in 8 directories)
      - Asian American Studies, 2012
        - 2012 Aug 14, aas20120814; 25 megabyte(s) (115 files in 7 directories)
      - Chicano/a Studies, 2012
        - 2012 Aug 14, chs20120814; 12.2 megabyte(s) (88 files in 4 directories)
    - Drama, Department of, 2011-2012; drama_2011-089
      - 2011 May 4, 264 megabyte(s) (323 files in 27 directories)
      - 2012 Feb 8, drama20120208; 81.6 megabyte(s) (432 files in 33 folders)
      - Division of Dance, 2012
        - 2012 Jul 24, dance20120724; 12.7 megabyte(s) (96 files in 10 directories)
    - East Asian Languages and Cultures, Department of, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 4, ealc_2011-090; 5.92 megabyte(s) (154 files in 21 directories)
      - 2012 Feb 8, asianlang20120208; 42.5 megabyte(s) (2979 files in 25 directories)
      - 2013 Feb 11, asianlang20130211; 60.5 megabyte(s) (4233 files in 22 directories)
    - Economics, Department of, 2011-2013
      - 2011 May 9-11, econ_2011-104; 1136.64 megabyte(s) (4177 files in 218 directories)
      - 2012 Mar 6, econ20120306; 643 megabyte(s) (8250 files in 209 directories)
      - 2013 Mar 1
    - English, Department of, 2011-2013; engl_2011-091
      - 2011 May 4, 24.8 megabyte(s) (774 files in 41 directories)